("Need You Now" by
Lady Antebellum)
- [Woman] Hey, sorry
I missed your call.
Just leave a message
after the beep.
(voicemail beeps)
- Hey, uh, it's me.
Still thinking about everything
tonight, and I don't know.
I just miss you so much.
Give me a call back if you can.
♪ Picture perfect memories
scattered all around the floor ♪
♪ Reachin' for the phone 'cause
I can't fight it anymore ♪
♪ And I wonder if I ever ♪
♪ Cross your mind ♪
♪ For me, it happens
all the time ♪
♪ It's a quarter after one ♪
♪ I'm all alone and
I need you now ♪
♪ Said I wouldn't call ♪
♪ But I lost all control
and I need you now ♪
♪ And I don't know
how I can do without ♪
♪ I just need you now ♪
♪ Another shot of whiskey,
can't stop lookin' at the door ♪
♪ Wishing you'd come sweeping
in the way you did before ♪
♪ And I wonder if I ever ♪
♪ Cross your mind ♪
♪ For me, it happens
all the time ♪
♪ It's a quarter after one ♪
♪ I'm little drunk
and I need you now ♪
♪ Said I wouldn't call ♪
♪ But I lost all control
and I need you now ♪
♪ And I don't know
how I can do without ♪
♪ I just need you now ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Yes, I'd rather
hurt than feel ♪
♪ Nothin' at all ♪
♪ It's a quarter after one ♪
♪ I'm all alone and
I need you now ♪
♪ And I said I wouldn't call ♪
♪ But I'm a little drunk
and I need you now ♪
♪ And I don't know
how I can do without ♪
♪ I just need you now ♪
♪ Oh, baby, I need you now ♪